You there?
Five Nights at Freddy's 2 is a horror, thriller film directed by Emma Tammi.
One year since the supernatural nightmare at Freddy Fazbear's Pizza, the stories about what transpired
there have been twisted into a campy local legend, inspiring the town's first ever Fazfest.
With the truth kept from her, Abby sneaks out to reconnect with Freddy, Bonnie, Chica, and Foxy, setting into motion a terrifying
series of events that will reveal dark secrets about the real origin of Freddy's, and unleash a decades-hidden horror.
Mike, played by Josh Hutcherson.
Abby, played by Piper Rubio.
Vanessa, played by Elizabeth Lail.
William Afton / Yellow Rabbit, played by Matthew Lillard.
Michael, played by Freddy Carter.
Mr. Berg, played by Wayne Knight.
Five Nights at Freddy's 2 is a 2025 American supernatural horror film based on the video game series Five
Nights at Freddy's created by Scott Cawthon and the sequel to the 2023 film adaptation.
The film was directed by Emma Tammi and written by Cawthon.
Josh Hutcherson, Elizabeth Lail, Piper Rubio, and Matthew Lillard reprise their roles from the
previous film, with Mckenna Grace, Wayne Knight, and Skeet Ulrich joining the cast.
Set a year and a half after the previous film, it follows Abby Schmidt (Rubio) as she gets manipulated by the
Marionette, an animatronic from the original Freddy Fazbear's Pizza who aims to plot revenge against parents.
Cawthon stated in August 2018 that there could be a second Five Nights at Freddy's film, based on
the events of the series' second video game, if the first film were successful.
Hutcherson revealed the development of a sequel in January 2024, with
Blumhouse Productions confirming it three months later.
Principal photography began in November 2024 and concluded in
February 2025 in New Orleans and surrounding communities.
Five Nights at Freddy's 2 premiered at the TCL Chinese Theater on December 2, 2025, and
was released in the United States by Universal Pictures on December 5.
Similar to its predecessor, the film received negative reviews from critics and was a commercial
success, grossing $237.8 million worldwide against a budget between $36–51 million.
The film explores themes of killer robot, pizzeria,
sequel, serial killer, security guard.
The tone is intense and uplifting and dark.